---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://opentdb.com/api.php?amount=10&category=9&difficulty=easy
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
      User-Agent:
      - Ruby
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Date:
      - Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:24:49 GMT
      Server:
      - Apache
      Expires:
      - Thu, 19 Nov 1981 08:52:00 GMT
      Cache-Control:
      - no-store, no-cache, must-revalidate
      Pragma:
      - no-cache
      Access-Control-Allow-Origin:
      - "*"
      Set-Cookie:
      - PHPSESSID=5a0d94d58d72f57dc9b4a02769ec8e90; path=/
      Upgrade:
      - h2
      Connection:
      - Upgrade
      Vary:
      - User-Agent
      Strict-Transport-Security:
      - max-age=31536000
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Content-Type:
      - application/json
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"response_code":0,"results":[{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        word represents the letter &#039;T&#039; in the NATO phonetic alphabet?","correct_answer":"Tango","incorrect_answers":["Target","Taxi","Turkey"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Nutella is produced
        by the German company Ferrero.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"How many colors
        are there in a rainbow?","correct_answer":"7","incorrect_answers":["8","9","10"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"A scientific study
        on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"According to
        Sherlock Holmes, &quot;If you eliminate the impossible, whatever remains,
        however improbable, must be the...&quot;","correct_answer":"Truth","incorrect_answers":["Answer","Cause","Source"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What company
        developed the vocaloid Hatsune Miku?","correct_answer":"Crypton Future Media","incorrect_answers":["Sega","Sony","Yamaha
        Corporation"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"When
        someone is cowardly, they are said to have what color belly?","correct_answer":"Yellow","incorrect_answers":["Green","Red","Blue"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Canadian
        $1 coin is colloquially known as a what?","correct_answer":"Loonie","incorrect_answers":["Boolie","Foolie","Moodie"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What is the French
        word for &quot;fish&quot;?","correct_answer":"poisson","incorrect_answers":["fiche","escargot","mer"]},{"category":"General
        Knowledge","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"The &ldquo;fairy&rdquo;
        type made it&rsquo;s debut in which generation of the Pokemon core series
        games?","correct_answer":"6th","incorrect_answers":["2nd","7th","4th"]}]}'
  recorded_at: Sun, 30 Apr 2023 06:24:49 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.1.0
